<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="78622" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="TransportPolicyAdjuster" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Set the desired vehicles count regardless of the route length!" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
TransportPolicyAdjuster is a mod that puts the power of transportation management firmly in your hands. Have you ever found yourself frustrated by the limitations of the "assigned vehicles" slider in your favorite transportation simulation game? Perhaps you wanted more control over the number of vehicles operating on a route, regardless of its length. With TransportPolicyAdjuster, you now have the freedom to fine-tune this aspect of gameplay according to your preferences.

Gone are the days of being constrained by arbitrary rules determining vehicle allocation based solely on route length. This mod allows you to set a range of 1 to a configurable maximum number for each type of transport vehicle in your virtual world. Whether you're managing buses, trams, subways, trains, ships, or airplanes, the choice is yours.

TransportPolicyAdjuster doesn't clutter your game with additional UI elements or complicated menus. Instead, it provides a streamlined settings page where you can easily adjust the maximum allowable number of vehicles for each transportation type. Want to flood your city streets with buses or fill your skies with airplanes? With this mod, the power to customize your transportation networks is now at your fingertips.

Whether you're a seasoned city planner looking for more control or a casual gamer seeking a more flexible gameplay experience, TransportPolicyAdjuster offers a simple yet powerful solution. Take charge of your transportation infrastructure like never before and watch your virtual world thrive under your expert management.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/SettingsPage.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/AssignedVehicles.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/NamedRoutes.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.5" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
Fixed mod for version 1.2.0f1
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/SonnyX/CS2-TransportPolicyAdjuster" />
</Publish>
